¶ Men. ¶
I hope you don't mind,
I used your toothbrush.
No problem.
Where'd you use it?
Nowhere your mouth hasn't been.
You are so beautiful.
Thank you.
Your-your hair.
Your-your eyes.
They're just amazing.
Charlie.
And this body...
it's just perfect.
Thank you.
So...
Why don't I want to have
sex with you anymore?
You don't?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no. It's okay.
I don't want to have sex
with you, either.
Oh, thank God.
I was feeling so guilty.
Me, too!
When did you know it was over?
Ah, about two weeks ago.
Remember? Alan took
Jake to the movies,
and we did it on the deck.
All I could think about
was picking up
the champagne bottle
and caving in your skull.
Were you angry with me?
No, no. It was more
just a way to kill time.
You know, fantasizing
if I could get away with it.
Interesting.
I fantasized about you
having a heart attack
or getting hit by a bus.
That way, I wouldn't
be a suspect,
and people would
feel sorry for me.
Smart.
So, when did you know?
It was in the limo, wasn't it?
Yep.
Yeah.
I could tell your
attention was wandering.
Every time I looked up,
you were somewhere else.
I hate to say it,
but I was making believe
you were another woman.
Well, that doesn't
necessarily mean it's over.
I pretended you were the
big blue chick from Avatar.
It's over.
So, what do we do now?
Part friends, I guess.
I'd like that.
It's getting kind of late.
You're welcome to
spend the night.
Oh, that's very sweet,
but I want to get as far
away from you as I can.
That's okay.
I just got Avatar on DVD.
So, we're all good?
Absolutely.
All right.
I'll go get dressed.
(Farts loudly)
You couldn't wait till I'm gone?
Didn't seem to be any point.
¶ Men, men, men, men, manly men, men, men ¶
¶ Ooh ¶
¶ Men, men, men, men, manly men ¶
¶ Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ¶
¶ Men, men, men, men, manly men, men, men ¶
¶ Ooh ¶
¶ Ah. ¶
¶ Men. ¶
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Morning.
Online poker?
Live girl-on-girl porn.
Really?
At 7:00 A.M.?
It's not 7:00 A.M. in Copenhagen.
How can you tell?
There's no windows.
Well, me, I like to start
my day with a cup of coffee.
Instant energy,
and it helps me poop.
Mm, mm, mm.
Somebody's having the
breakfast of champions.
They say it's the most important
meal of the day.
Oh, please tell me Courtney
isn't up in your bedroom
while you're looking
at this stuff.
Courtney went home.
We broke up.
Oh. And you're trying
to fill the void
and mend your broken heart
at danishmunchers.com.
Yeah. Something like that.
So, what happened?
Nothing happened.
It just ran its course.
Wow, that's hard to imagine.
She's so hot.
Let me tell you something, Alan.
For every gorgeous woman
in the world,
there's a guy out there
who's tired of banging her.
But that guy's never me.
I got to get out of the house.
Maybe go to the movies.
Is Jake here?
Uh, no.
He's having a party
over at his mom's
house tonight.
Oh, damn.
Did I forget his birthday?
Oh, no, no, no. It's just one
of those teenage parties.
Uh, but for the record,
his birthday was six months ago,
and yes, you did forget it.
Oh, man.
How old was he?
Sixteen.
Huh.
No wonder he keeps
asking to borrow my car.
I guess I'll just go
to the movies by myself.
You want some company?
Hello? That's why
I was asking about Jake.
Good morning, ladies.
Charlie: No masturbating
in the kitchen!
What do you say we go someplace
a little quieter?
¶ Men. ¶
(playing note)
Hey, what ya working on?
It's a jingle
for a new kids'
breakfast cereal.
Oh, cool. Can I hear it?
I guess.
Picture this over animated
dancing monkeys and zebras.
Got it.
(Playing dark, dramatic tune)
¶ Start your day
with a big hooray ¶
¶ chocolate diddlers ¶
¶ bowl of fun for everyone ¶
¶ chocolate diddlers,
chocolate diddlers ¶
¶ Yum. ¶
Uh...
Well, I like the lyric.
Uh, you know, it's kind of...
It's upbeat, uh, celebratory.
You know, "hooray, fun, yum."
Um, if I had a note...
Uh, it would be the music.
What about it?
Uh, well, it doesn't say,
"yummy breakfast treat"
so much as it says,
"my puppy's dead."
(Sighs)
Yeah, I've been
a little down lately.
I know. I know. But, uh...
But keep workin' on it.
Okay.
Well, I'm off.
Where you going?
Uh, to have drinks with Lindsey
and a few of her friends.
Have a good time.
You know,
you're welcome to tag along.
I mean, a couple
of these women are divorced,
and got a few miles on 'em,
but they've been liposucked
to within an inch of their
lives, so they present well.
That's okay, I got to work.
You sure?
For somebody like you,
it'd be shooting fish
in a barrel.
Although in this case,
the fish would be 40-year-old,
neurotic soccer moms,
and the barrel would be
a Bennigan's in Encino.
Sounds tempting, but I'll pass.
Okay, good night.
(Playing dark, dramatic tune)
Honestly,
think more bouncy.
Happy. "I love
chocolate diddlers, yay!"
Got it.
(Door closes)
Okay, bouncy, happy.
(Playing bouncy tune)
¶ C is for chocolate ¶
¶ D is diabetes ¶
¶ Do your kids a favor ¶
¶ Buy a box of Wheaties ¶
¶ Chocolate diddlers, yay! ¶
Okay.
That's a good day's work.
¶ Men. ¶
Hi.
Charlie.
Veronica.
How's life treating
you, Veronica?
Not too bad.
How about you?
Well, that depends on
which answer you want.
There's more than one?
Well, I could give you the
"everything's hunky-dory.
"I live at the beach,
drive a nice car,
and have a python
in my pants" answer.
Or I could tell you the truth.
You have an inchworm
in your pants?
No, the python part's true.
Okay, so what is
wrong with Charlie?
All right, fine.
I'll tell you.
Two bourbons, straight up.
You want anything?
I'm good.
I'll spare you the details
of my selfish, narcissistic,
soul-sucking mother,
my deadbeat,
oddly effeminate brother,
and the future organ donor
we call my nephew.
Okay.
And just to bring you
up to speed
on my recent
romantic adventures,
about this time last year,
I was engaged
to the greatest gal
I'd ever met.
Uh-huh.
So, what went wrong?
Hard to pinpoint.
It could've been
my-my drinking,
my compulsive gambling...
Or it could've been me
sleeping with her best friend.
I can see why it'd
be hard to pinpoint.
I know, right?
So, anyway,
she dumped me for a nice guy,
but I got right back
on the horse
and married
a drug-addled stripper.
And that didn't work out?
Not for the reasons
you'd think.
She was already married.
Whoops.
So I figured maybe
I'd take a break for a while
from the dating
and just see hookers.
Sure.
Yeah, I'm aware
of the social stigma,
but I like to think
of prostitution
as trickle-down economics.
Actually, it's all
kind of trickle-down.
It's very republican,
when you think about it.
Uh-huh.
You know what? I will
have another drink.
So anyway, I take
the moral high ground
and try to break up
with the 47-year-old,
so I won't be tempted to hit on
her hot, 20-year-old daughter.
Laudable.
But surprise, surprise,
mom breaks up with me first
'cause she finds out
I still have feelings
for this crazy broad
that stalks me.
Next thing I know,
my ex-girlfriend
gets out of prison,
I'm right in the middle of...
Can I stop you a sec?
Sure.
Thank you.
For what?
I came in here tonight
because I was angry at
my pig of a boyfriend.
But after listening to you,
I realize I was unfair to him.
There's something below "pig".
Okay.
Well, I'm glad I could help.
How's life treating you?
In what universe did I not hear
everything you just said?
Nobody likes an eavesdropper.
¶ Men. ¶
(music playing)
Dude, your party
is a total sausage fest.
Hey, you're the one who said,
"Let's not invite
the girls we know.
Let's meet new girls".
Exactly. So did
you invite them?
Who?
The girls we don't know.
Dude, how can I invite them
if I don't know them?
Good point, dude.
Guess who brought beer!
Oh, God.
Wow. This is
a total sausage fest.
Told you, dude.
Hey, gang, there's hot
quesadillas in the kitchen.
Charlie? What the hell
are you doing here?
Well, I heard Jake
was having a party.
I thought I'd stop by.
To hang out
with a bunch of teenagers?
Yeah, that occurred to me.
The cabdriver thought
it was a good idea.
And it's a really long drive.
There's something
seriously wrong with you.
Get help.
First I got to get another cab.
Taxi!
It was nice of him
to bring beer.
He's a crazy bastard, but
he's got good manners.
Charlie:
Taxi!
¶ Men. ¶
(loud knocking)
Charlie:
Knock, knock!
Not a good time!
(Slurring): Alan, you're supposed
to say, "who's there?"
That's okay, I'll say it.
Who's there?
Go away, Charlie.
(Door opens)
Go away Charlie who?
I am very sorry.
What do you want?
I just wanted
to give you a heads-up
that your ex-wife's gonna be
calling you in the morning,
and it's not gonna be
a pretty call.
Hi, Lindsey.
Hi, Charlie.
You're a saint
for having sex with my brother.
Okay.
Good night.
No, really...
It's like taking a bird
with a-a busted wing
and putting him in a shoebox
and feeding him
with an eyedropper.
You know he's never gonna fly,
but you give it your best shot.
Alan's the bird.
What are you doing?
Just resting.
Your brother needs help.
I know.
And-and for the record,
I believe I will fly again.
¶ Men. ¶
What do you want me
to do, Judith?
He's a drunk
with a lot of money...
You can't control
people like that.
The best you can do is
stay on their good side
so you can inherit their house
after they crap out their liver.
As a matter of fact, I have
given it a lot of thought.
Oh, oh, fine,
I will talk to him about it.
Okay, okay, bye.
Still think you're
getting the house, huh?
What?
Not important.
Charlie:
Alan?
Yeah?
Why did I wake up in your bed?
You passed out there.
Did we break any biblical laws?
No. Uh, Lindsey and I
went up to your room.
Ew, gross.
Did you have sex in my bed?
No. Actually,
the romance of the evening
pretty much evaporated
after you curled up at our feet
like a drunken Labrador.
Well, that's good.
Let's play it safe and take
those sheets out of rotation.
Uh, just to put it
on the record,
I'm officially telling you,
on behalf of my ex-wife,
don't ever do that again.
Don't ever do what again?
Doesn't matter...
I've fulfilled my obligation.
You know, Alan,
I'm starting to think I'm not
living up to my full potential.
Really?
You think you can
hump and drink even more?
No.
Well, maybe.
The thing is,
I woke up this morning
and there were these
little voices in my head
telling me to get help.
Get help.
Lyndsey:
Your brother needs help.
Alan:
I will fly again.
Better I realize it
before somebody
has to point it out, huh?
Mm-hmm, no doubt.
So, what are you gonna do
with this newfound insight?
Well, I think it might be time
to go back to my shrink.
Mm. Talk about your issues.
Renew my prescriptions.
Much more in character.
¶ Men. ¶
(door opens)
Come on in, Charlie.
Thanks.
Well, it's been a while.
How you doing?
Good. Good.
Really? You usually only come to
see me when your hair's on fire
and someone's chasing you
with gasoline.
(Chuckles)
That almost happened to me once.
Thank God I was able
to pee on the matches.
So, what's going on?
Well, I just recently broke up
with this terrific gal,
and I guess I've been in
kind of an emotional tailspin.
Mm-hmm. Been drinking
heavier than usual?
Just the occasional
glass of wine with dinner.
Uh-huh. And how many dinners
have you had today?
Three.
So far.
Okay. Go on.
And it's not just this breakup.
For the last couple of years,
I've been trying really hard
to have
a meaningful relationship.
You know,
as opposed to picking up
some pretty little thing for
a quick bag, shag and skedaddle.
"Bag, shag and skedaddle."
That's charming.
Anyway, no matter how hard I try
to have something more lasting,
more meaningful, the end result
is always the same.
At some point, I got
to consider the possibility
that the problem might be me.
That's not a bad instinct.
I mean, if I'm doing something
wrong with all these women,
it'd probably be helpful
if I had a clue what it was.
Well, if you had to guess,
what would you say
you're doing wrong?
I don't know.
I love too much?
Guess again.
I'm afraid of intimacy?
Do you believe that to be true?
Not really.
I just hear it all the time.
Dr. Phil, movies,
TV shows, ex-girlfriends.
Let me ask you something.
What do you think being
truly intimate with a woman is?
Uh...
Not using a condom?
Wow.
What?
I'm sorry.
I-I didn't expect that.
But what I'm trying
to point you to
is the kind of intimacy
where you feel safe enough
to be completely honest
with a woman,
to tell her how you really feel.
Oh, come on! Nobody cares
how you really feel.
And what's a guy
like me feel anyway?
I'll tell you...
Tired, hungry, horny, hungover,
happy, sad and pissed off.
And sad and pissed off
only come into play
because I'm horny, hungry,
hungover and tired.
You know what?
Let's table the intimacy
discussion for the moment
and talk about
your other relationships.
What other relationships?
Well, if I recall,
we've spoken at great length
about your feelings
towards your mother,
your brother and your nephew.
Pissed off, pissed off, sad.
Sure.
How about non-familial
relationships?
What, you mean like friends?
Yes.
Then why don't you just say friends?
I've got the diplomas, Charlie.
I like to use them.
Okay, well, the answer
to your question is, uh...
I don't really have
that many friends.
Well, how many friends
would you say you have?
You know, I'm starting to feel
a little pissed off right now.
Do you have any friends,
Charlie?
Oh, come on. I'm a grown man.
I have acquaintances.
Do you spend time
with these acquaintances?
For what?
To talk about my feelings?
I'm not one to indulge
in a lot of chitchat
unless I feel like
it's gonna get me laid.
I'm just saying it might be nice
to have some relationships
in your life
that aren't based solely
on you trying
to get someone into bed.
You have no idea
what I'm talking about, do you?
Not a clue.
Okay, now I'm pissed off
and sad.
Maybe you didn't have
enough dinner.
¶ Men. ¶
Thank you.
Are you sure
you should be drinking
if you're on medication?
Nah, she wouldn't
give me anything.
Said I'd abuse it.
Where does that come from?
One more.
So, uh, did you get anything
out of the session?
Not really. She
kept saying I need
to develop relationships
that aren't about sex.
You know, I can see
the wisdom in that.
Well, sure you can.
You didn't get laid
the last nine years
of a 12-year marriage.
Not true.
There were birthdays.
Let's pretend for a second
the shrink is right.
What am I supposed to do?
Just somehow go out and
make new guy friends?
Who does that?
Couldn't hurt to try.
Hey, there. How are you?
Good. You?
I've already lost interest.
Well, I can't fault you
for trying.
I mean, I'm not against
having a friend in theory,
but I'm a 43-year-old man
who's kind of set in his ways.
Where am I supposed to
go meet this new buddy?
Did you consider you could have
a woman as a friend?
Alan, have you not
been listening?
She said no sex.
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
I don't have
many friends, either.
You don't have
any friends.
Yeah, well, neither do you.
But that's my choice.
You... you're just
a social pariah.
And you're a malignancy
on the ass of mankind.
So, you want to pick up
a pizza on the way home?
Pizza, really?
Fine, what do you want?
Um, I was thinking Chinese.
We just had Chinese.
How about ribs?
Oh, great, but I'm
a little low on cash.
What's "a little low" mean?
Nothing.
All right, fine, I'll buy,
but I get to pick the movie.
Oh, we don't have to watch a movie...
I TiVo'd Glee.
Terrific.
I'm alone and miserable,
and you want to torture me
with hot chicks
in cheerleading outfits.
Singing hot chicks.
It's wang chung week.
For God's sake, Alan.
Why don't you just put on
a pair of ass-less chaps
and get it over with?
I'm not gay, I'm metrosexual.
That's just a gay man
who can't get laid.
¶ Men. ¶
(On TV):
¶ Everybody have fun tonight ¶
¶ everybody wang chung tonight ¶
The tall blonde chick
in the red tracksuit
is really starting
to freak me out.
(Singing along with TV):
¶ Everybody wang chung tonight ¶
¶ Everybody have fun ¶
Mercedes:
¶ Deep in the world tonight... ¶
I love Mercedes.
You go, girl!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com